Hi, I'm Lori Schneider with Figs Catering in Austin, Texas.
Today I am going to show you how to make a spaghetti squash casserole with a pink and almond crust.
I've been in the culinary industry for about 13 years.
One of my favorite things to cook with in the Fall time and it is Fall where we are right now is spaghetti squash.
Spaghetti squash is really unique and different because it really absorbs the flavors of things that you put with it.
So for this casserole, we have first off baked our spaghetti squash and then we made kind of a cream, egg and rosemary, sun dried tomato mixture that we mixed in with our cooked spaghetti squash in a casserole dish.
On top of that, we went ahead and made some buttered pink crumbs along with some almonds and that is going to provide the really nice crust that you see there.
I really like serving this dish because not a lot of people have tried spaghetti squash because it is a unique product.
So go ahead and give it a try.
It is a lot of fun to work with and it tastes great.